https://www.pressharbor.com/privacy-policy/

The PressHarbor hosting service operated by Rackshare LLC (“RACKSHARE”) respects the privacy of its customers and visitors to this website. Your personal information is only collected, used and disclosed by RACKSHARE in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
By using our website or purchasing our Services (as defined below), you are expressly consenting to and have knowledge of the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, as identified in this Privacy Policy. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website.
1. INFORMATION COLLECTED
We only collect personal information about you when you specifically and knowingly provide it on our website or to our customer service representatives via telephone. If you request information or purchase domain name, email webhosting or other services (the “Services”) you will be asked to provide personal information. This information may include your:
name
address
telephone and fax numbers
email address
username
password, and
credit card information
2. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
RACKSHARE only collects and uses your information for the following purposes:
To establish and maintain a responsible commercial relationship with you and to provide ongoing service. For example, when you purchase Services, we collect information that allows us to confirm your identity and credit history so that we can accurately bill and collect payment for the Services
To understand your needs and preferences. For example, we maintain a record of the products and services you receive from us, and we may ask for additional information so that we can serve you better
To develop, enhance, market or provide products and services. For example, we analyze how our customers use our products and services, so that we can understand how to improve them. From time to time, we may review and analyze your use of our products and services to help us provide better product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you
To manage and develop our business and operations. For example, we analyze customer usage of our networks and facilities to help us manage them efficiently and plan for future growth
To meet legal and regulatory requirements. For example, we may collect information in response to a court order
3. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
There are a variety of circumstances where we may need to disclose some personal information about you. Here are some examples:
We may disclose your personal information to:
a person who, in the reasonable judgment of RACKSHARE, is seeking the information as your agent. For example, we may provide information about your account to your legal representative if we are satisfied that that individual is requesting the information on your behalf
RACKSHARE parent companies or subsidiaries to help us serve you better and provide you with services
a company or individual employed by RACKSHARE to perform functions on our behalf, such as research or data processing
an agent used by RACKSHARE to evaluate your credit worthiness or to collect your account
a credit reporting agency
a public authority, agent of a public authority or law enforcement agency
ANY DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO A THIRD PARTY IS CONFIDENTIAL AND THE INFORMATION SHALL BE USED ONLY FOR THE PURPOSE FOR WHICH IT WAS DISCLOSED.
4. RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
The account or membership information you provide when registering with us is stored in our secure databases as long as you are a customer of RACKSHARE. You must notify RACKSHARE if you no longer want your information to be retained by us. If you contact us with a question or comment, any information identifying you is only kept long enough for us to provide you with a response, unless we are required to keep it for a longer period of time.
Please note that it may be impossible to delete your information completely without some residual information remaining in our databases.
5. PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
In order to protect your personal information and your right to privacy, RACKSHARE:
uses a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Server Certificate
uses servers that are protected by firewalls, which are frequently updated to enhance security
protects the confidentiality of your personal information when dealing with other companies
strives to keep your personal information as accurate and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes identified above
uses other appropriate security safeguards with respect to its databases, computer networks and systems, and
will honour any request you may make for access to your personal information
6. ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION AND YOUR ACCESS TO IT
RACKSHARE relies on the accuracy of the information provided by you, but accepts responsibility for the management and confidentiality of the personal information it collects. Please contact our Information Administrator at accounts@rackshare.com to:
change or confirm your personal information
have your information removed from our databases, or
speak to someone about RACKSHARE’s information-handling practices
Categories
FAQ
News
Tutorials
